Please enter your password.
Listen, press one.
Send, press two.
Check receipt, press three.
Bo, it's Mr. Granger.
I called as soon as I heard.
I'm so sorry.
I know I've
never met your mom,
but if you were any
reflection of her,
she must have been
someone really special.
I just want you to know, uh,
I understand the pain
you're feeling right now.
It feels kind of like
the world is ending.
And when I've
been in that spot,
I just wish someone
had been there to tell me
to not let the now
disrupt the future.
That scholarship proves you're one in
a million, Bo, don't forget that.
I'm here if you need anything.
Don't ever hesitate to call.
End of message.
Delete, press seven.
Save, press nine.
Deleted.
Okay.
That the one you want?
You could swap it out.
Yeah,
I'll keep this one.
All right, can you show
everyone what card you have?
Not me, just show
everyone what you have.
Sweet, so I want you to put
that card in your shirt pocket,
really make sure there's no
way I can see it or touch it.
All right, all right, so I'm gonna
take another card, all right?
Four of hearts.
Now, go ahead and hold
your hand over your card.
Really make sure there's
no way I can touch it.
Yeah, for sure.
Oh, wait.
Ah, you were just a little too slow,
so you should have my heart.
Weird, uh, does anyone
else have the card?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
No way!
That's insane.
How did you do it?
As you can see,
there's no string at all, all right?
What's your name?
Uh, Holly.
You can grab it, Holly.
How did you do that?
You ready, T?
Yeah.
All done for the day.
What you reading?
Hatchet.
Oh, okay.
I read that forever ago.
I almost cried when he first...
Stop!
I'm only
three chapters in.
Oh, my bad.
My bad.
Let's head out.
Okay.
You about to ruin my book.
I had
a long day today.
Made this ring levitate in
front of this girl's face.
Remember the trick I showed you?
Uh-huh.
T, stop leaving your
stuff in the living room.
You forgot the mail.
Thank you.
Georgi.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, are you
around tonight?
Yeah, you working?
Um, yeah,
I'm making Tina dinner now,
but if you wouldn't mind
getting her to bed?
Yeah, no problem.
You have a good day?
I did, yeah.
I just got back
from Graffiti,
finished a whole
chapter,
which somehow feels like
I've been to war and back.
If I stare at the page for one more second,
my eyes are gonna bleed.
You?
Nothing,
it was fine.
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna take a shower
real quick and
then I'll be over.
Okay, thank you.
Yo.
There he is.
What up, Bo?
What's up, man?
Hello.
What's up, buddy?
What's up, dude?
Luna's in the office.
Okay.
Luna.
Bo.
Thank God. I'm having an
"I need drugs" situation.
Get in here.
I mean, DJs?
I don't know what they're doing.
They will ask for a blow-up
doll two months in advance
and then drugs day of.
Like, I don't know
how I'm supposed to
turn that around
for you, buddy.
This what your ride
is gonna look like?
Oh, God, no.
I'm a beer and pizza gal.
This? This is nonsense.
I am so over this gig.
Me, too. Later.
Yeah. Cheers, dude. Be well.
All right.
Oh, so, we don't get a trick?
Oh.
What's that?
It's my wallet!
He just gave me
my fucking wallet.
You...
When the hell
did he take it?
Later.
This is my phone!
What the hell!
What are you
laughing at?
Are you Bo?
Yeah, get in.
Okay.
Hey. Hi,
I'm, uh, Noah.
I got your number
from some friends.
So, it's, uh, $60?
For three. Yeah.
Three. Can I ask,
is it one molly per person?
Or should I...
Do you think I should get more?
Do you sell coke?
Can I also get coke?
Can you even do
molly with coke?
I met these girls, and it's kind
of cool to know a guy, you know?
Sounds kind of dumb
when you say it, but...
Hey, listen, man,
whatever you want.
But, honestly, don't buy
drugs to impress girls.
I'll take
the molly though.
$60.
The ATM would
only give me $100.
I know we said three,
but I've got $100 here.
Um, that's no worries,
I can give you five for...
One...
- Shit!
- Hands up!
What are you doing back here?
What'd you just have in your hands?
Uh, nothing...
Nothing, sir.
Why did he
take off running?
I think he was
just scared, sir.
If I search your pockets,
am I gonna find anything illegal?
No, sir.
Turn around.
Hands on your head.
Interlace your fingers.
Where'd you put it?
I saw you stash something in your pocket.
I don't know what you're talking
about, sir. I don't have anything.
You put something
in your pocket!
I don't have
anything, sir.
See anything?
Get the fuck
out of here.
Oh, my God!
No, no, no, no!
Bo, I'm sorry!
Don't pour water on hot oil, okay?
It can start a fire!
Okay, I'm sorry.
I was just trying to
make you breakfast.
What was this?
Bacon.
Man, let's...
Let's clean this out.
I'll show you how to make it
the way you like, all right?
Okay.
Sorry.
Come here.
You scared me.
Sorry.
Here, grab the soap.
What's up?
Come on in.
You have been
doing good.
Keep it up and these assholes
will be working for you one day.
Everything else good?
Yeah,
just dealing the shit out.
Nothing much else
really going on.
Okay.
You got a girl
these days?
Nah, just
my little sister.
Well, actually, I'm meeting
with this girl tomorrow.
It's our
first time out.
No shit.
Where'd you meet her?
Just out and about.
Ooh! Attaboy.
You know what?
First date is on me.
No, no, no,
I can't take that.
Oh, please,
no worries, man.
I was wondering if you could
do me a favor though?
You still selling
over at Daedalus?
Yeah,
it's my biggest pull.
I've been hearing there's a new
coke supplier in the area.
They got someone
selling there, too.
You mind keeping
an eye out?
Sure.
Perfect.
I just need the name
of the supplier.
Well, I'll let you
know what I find out.
Sounds good.
Have fun
on that date.
Thanks.
All right.
Hey, did that guy
just buy from you?
No.
No? Well, it looked like
he just bought from you.
Nah, man, I think
you're mistaken.
Oh, come on, I'm just trying to party,
have a good time, you know.
Sorry. Sorry, man.
Well, I mean, all that money,
I'm sure you've got something.
I don't got
anything for you.
Come on, man...
I said...
I said
I can't help you.
Fine.
Fucking punk ass.
Yo.
Look like the supplier's
name is Maurice.
Yep.
Hey.
Uh...
Good to see you again.
We really didn't get a
chance to meet last time.
Hence me giving
you my number.
Right.
Yeah, I was just
getting off work,
that day when I
saw you performing.
So, you work
on Larchmont?
Yeah, yeah,
Crumbs bakery.
I sell giant cupcakes
a couple days a week,
but I'm at community college
racking up credits.
Awesome.
Oh, uh, here, sorry.
Thank you.
So, you do magic?
I mean, a little.
I'm getting pretty good at it.
You know, I have never seen
a cute magician before.
I'm starving.
He sent a card on my birthday,
but that's about it.
I haven't seen him
in about a year.
Yeah, he moved out fast.
Like, crazy fast.
Well, I mean, at least Arizona's not
that far if you wanted to visit.
That's what he said.
Yeah.
It's funny though,
'cause, like, I get it, you know.
Like, my mom has
always been a handful.
And Arizona, it's far enough away
for him to get away from her,
but close enough to
still come see me.
Not that he does,
but whatever.
It doesn't
really bother me,
but my mom is definitely still
dealing with the whole thing.
And she really
needs me right now.
But once my mom is better,
I can figure out where I
wanna finish up school.
Mmm.
God, I'm sorry. I feel like
I've been talking for hours.
No, I asked. It's fine.
What about you?
Well, my dad passed a while back,
and my mom passed last year,
so it's just me and my little sister, Tina,
the love of my life.
She's such
a smart kid, you know.
I just wish I
can move her into
a neighborhood
with a better school.
Yeah. Surround her
with better people.
Yeah.
- Uh, she's gonna be something big.
- I know it.
I grew up in
a school district,
and, honestly, except for one
teacher I had, nobody cared.
And I just...
Do you need to get that?
No.
It's fine.
Get it if you need to.
Okay, it'll just
be a second.
Yeah.
Totally, man.
I'll be right there.
No, it's cool.
I'm the worst.
I'm sorry, I gotta go.
Society of magic ruining
a perfectly good first date?
I'm sorry.
I'm kidding,
it's fine.
I promise.
Let's do this again, though.
Please.
Ought to be good enough
for you, young buck.
Hey. Ready?
What's going on?
Found out where
this Maurice guy lives.
Homie moves into our backyard and
starts selling coke like I don't exist.
I mean, we're gonna
pay him a little visit.
Talk to him about etiquette.
Let's go.
Put that shit out.
Smoke after.
Yeah, put that shit out, man,
smoke it after.
What the fuck?
Sit down, loser!
Sit down!
Maurice, right?
Check to make sure
no one else is here.
Get up.
So, here's what I
don't understand.
You moved to this neighborhood,
started selling,
and never thought to
introduce yourself?
Man, listen, I don't
give a fuck about who you are.
See, that's the problem
with kids like you.
You come out hot-tempered
and bad-mannered.
There's no respect.
I don't even know you.
And I don't need
to know you.
Maurice, now don't
play me like that.
You can't say
you've never heard of me,
because you guys are out
there telling people
that your shit
is cheaper than mine.
So, you know me well enough
to compare yourself.
That's not good business.
Where the fuck
do you come from
where people do
business like that?
West Covina?
Yo... You know what?
Why don't you just get the
fuck outta here, old man?
Here, here, here,
take some chips with you.
Oh, shit.
Wow! What...
I mean...
That's what
we're gonna do now.
Okay. See, even your boys
are talking like you.
Sit the fuck down! Now!
You gotta lead
by example.
Maurice. Maurice.
You and I, we could be friends.
We really could.
And if you don't like me, we
could at least be co-workers.
And we both know you don't always
have to like your co-workers.
So, your options.
You can go back to wherever
the fuck you came from,
or you can get comfortable, stay right
here, sell my shit, and kick me 30%.
Think about it.
Let me know.
All this weed
and no snacks?
Man, this party's whack.
Fuck!
Man, get the fuck up.
That gun slipped out of
your hand like some cartoon shit.
We gotta put sticky
tape on it next time.
Yo, you're one of my boys now.
Word?
I never thought
it'd get dangerous.
You guys never done
something like this before?
A stick-up? No.
Hell no. And that's
what I liked about Angelo.
I mean, he didn't seem
like the gangbanger.
Just a cool guy who'd help me make
money off kids who wanted to party.
I don't know, this is
turning into something
I would've
never signed up for.
And I thought this whole
thing would be temporary.
I mean, a year flashes by
and I'm still a drug dealer.
I need to get out
of this, Georgi.
Now.
Eight of clubs, okay?
Keep it facing me.
So, the card is
gonna stay in your hand.
I'm not messing with it.
This is all you.
All right. So, I need you
to name another card.
Any card besides
the eight of clubs.
Three of diamonds?
Three of diamonds.
You sure?
You can change your mind.
You're making all the decisions.
Three of diamonds.
Okay.
Turn it around.
Oh, my...
No way!
Are you kidding me?
- Uh, hey!
- Hey, what's up?
Not much.
What are you up to?
Just out performing.
Are you working tonight?
Yeah.
Cool, where at?
Uh, NoHo, maybe hit
CityWalk in a bit.
Tourists love magic.
Damn, I was just,
you know,
seeing if you wanted to
catch a movie or something.
Uh, maybe tomorrow night,
though?
I could make you
dinner maybe?
All right.
Are you gonna be working?
I can pick you up.
Perfect. Oh, shit,
I have a customer. Text me.
Oh, oh...
Okay, any one
you want, all right?
Okay.
I want you to sign
your name on that card.
You don't need to
hide it from me,
we all should know
which one is yours.
Shuffle your card into the deck.
Get it lost in there.
Perfect.
And there's a lot of things in
our lives that can trap us.
It could be a person,
a problem.
There're so many things
that can wall us in.
But these barriers
only exist if we let them.
We can do whatever we want if
we just believe we're able to.
There's a card in here
with your name on it, right?
Uh-huh.
Let's say
51 of these cards
are too scared to
trust themselves.
Too afraid to believe that they
can do whatever they want.
Okay.
Now, your card,
your card knows
there's no wall,
no limit, no barrier.
Okay.
Is that your card?
Oh, my God.
No, it's not.
So, where did you meet?
On Larchmont.
He was performing
outside my work.
I like your nose ring.
Thanks.
I want one,
but Bo says they're ugly.
Oh, does he?
He said so.
So, is Bo your boyfriend?
Uh, we actually
just kind of met.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Yeah.
Three of them.
Three?
Who are these boys?
Jacob, Elijah and Daniel.
I'm gonna die alone.
I thought
boys might like you.
Well, you need to let them
know you got a big brother
who'll beat them up
if they ever get rude.
Okay.
So, she's a
lot cooler than you.
I have no idea
how this happened.
Yeah, well, family dinner is a
totally normal second date.
Good job there.
Was that bad?
You're fine.
You guys are cute.
Yo.
You weren't
picking up.
Oh, my bad. My phone is
charging in my room.
Oh, my bad.
Hello there, ladies.
I'm Angelo.
I work with Bo.
Hi, I'm Tina.
I'm Holly.
Georgi.
Very nice to meet you.
You must be
Bo's little sister?
Yeah, and Holly is
maybe-Bo's-girlfriend.
And Georgi's our friend.
Well, you have a good one
on your hands here.
I'm so sorry for interrupting, but I
just need to talk with Bo for a minute.
Chat outside, real quick?
Yeah.
What's up?
So, that motherfucker Maurice didn't
take my warning too seriously.
The dude's back out
there selling again.
Like, really, man?
We hear he's partying nearby.
Ought to catch him on his way out.
Right now?
We're in the car.
Hurry up.
Uh, hey, guys.
I have to head out
with Angelo for a second.
I like him.
Um, can you watch Tina
for, like, a few hours?
Yeah.
I can stay, too.
I mean, I don't wanna put
you out or anything,
I'm sure you've
got things to do.
I don't mind.
Honestly, I'd rather
stay if that's cool?
Please stay.
We'll see you
when you get back.
Thanks.
Hey. What was
he doing here?
Yeah. It's weird.
Yep.
It's cool.
Always the same with me.
Why are we leaving?
It was fun.
'Cause I'm fucking tired.
You can stay if you want to.
I don't even care.
You're my ride.
Well, then I guess
it's time to go home.
God damn it.
- Fuck! Fuck!
- Come on, baby.
- Damn it!
- Let's go. Let's go.
Let me go, man.
Grab the tarp
from under the sink.
I thought we
had a deal, man?
Man, we had no deal
about nothing.
See, this is why I
fucking kidnapped you.
Look, man, if it's about
a percentage, then fine.
Homie, homie, homie.
This is not about a percentage anymore.
You are here because
we made an agreement,
and then you decided
that you were above it.
Now, how the fuck you think
that makes me feel?
Put the tarp down.
You right-handed
or left-handed?
Am I what?
Are you right-handed
or left-handed?
I'm a leftie.
A southpaw?
I feel like
you're fuckin' lying.
Maybe not.
Tighten that
around his left arm.
In case you're wondering,
I'm not gonna kill you tonight.
You know what they used to do to
liars and thieves back in the day?
Wait, wait.
Hey! Come on, man, wait.
They'd cut a hand off.
Spread 'em out.
Wait... Come on, man.
Wait, what are you...
As clean as you can.
What?
No.
Why the fuck not?
I can't. I'm sorry.
Hey, Bo! This dude
does not respect us.
He doesn't give
a fuck about us.
And if we don't show him who
we are, he will come after us.
Whose side
are you on, Bo?
Come on. Come on, Bo.
Come on.
Come on, man.
Please, please, please.
Don't do this, man, please.
Okay?
I'm asking you.
Please don't do it, man.
Come on, don't do it,
man, please.
Please, please,
no, don't do it, man, please.
Please, man,
don't do it, okay?
don't do this, I'm beggin'.
Let's go.
Come on, please,
please, please, please, please.
His hand or yours, Bo.
Please don't do this. Please,
please, please. I'm begging you.
Please, please,
don't do this.
Bo!
Fuck!
You're gonna have to
do it harder than that.
No!
There you go.
You're fucking done.
If I hear that
you're selling again,
I'm gonna kill you
and every person you know.
Now, get the fuck
out of my house.
Let's go.
There's
gonna be a little more
business with Maurice
out of the picture.
You can handle
a key, right?
Yeah. Of course.
Boom.
Your normal
re-up's in there, too,
but you're gonna be working
with a lot more money,
so pay attention.
Oh...
I'm having a party at
the crib this weekend.
You should come through.
Bring your girl if you want.
If not, a bunch
will already be there.
Word.
Hey.
Why don't you
take my bed?
You don't need to
sleep on the couch.
Oh, shut up.
We can sleep
in the same bed.
Hey, uh, you want
a T-shirt or something?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, uh, thanks for
watching T tonight.
Oh, um,
what kind of cookies are you going to make?
Or are you gonna make a cake?
What makes you think
I'm baking something?
Because you have two
boxes of baking soda.
Oh, uh...
I'm not sure.
We'll figure out something.
Holy shit.
How much is that?
It's almost two kilos.
One of Angelo's
cut with baking soda.
This is a bad idea.
Selling all this,
I could pay Angelo his cut
and still walk
away with $15,000.
That's enough money
to get out.
Even if you
sell all this,
you really think Angelo's
gonna let you leave?
I don't know.
I hope.
I know it's not my
place to say this,
but there's no one else
here to say it to you.
I don't want you
to do this.
It's too dangerous.
I'm sorry.
It's already done.
Hey!
I'd like to re-up.
Or reorder.
Hey.
Wait, what?
What happened?
Where are you?
I can come over.
No, that's fine.
I'll meet you
at my place.
Hey.
Thanks.
She doesn't mean it.
It's just the divorce
that's still hurting her.
And I don't know,
when she drinks,
she just has a hard
time moving on. It's...
But she hits you.
I mean, I saw your
bruises the other night.
No one deserves that.
You can stay here as
long as you need to.
I mean, it's not
the Four Seasons,
but we try to keep
it pretty clean...
Sorry.
I'm never the girl with the
mascara running down her face.
Thank you.
Morning.
You sleep okay?
What is that?
What?
That thing
in your arm?
Oh, uh...
It's part of an effect.
But what is it?
It looks
kind of infected.
It's not that bad.
Bo, for a magic trick?
Why would you do
that to yourself?
The first time I ever saw a magic trick,
I was with my mom and dad
on the Venice Boardwalk.
And there was this guy, this old Italian
guy with this little Jack Russell.
He had this small
stand where he performed.
He did a lot of
card and coin stuff,
but there was
this one thing he did
that just stuck
with me forever.
He took a pocket knife and pressed
it into the center of his hand.
It went through his skin
with a hard push.
Popped through
the other side.
He held his hand
right in front of my face.
It didn't make
any sense, you know.
It looked like it was
going straight through.
So, he asked me
to pull it out.
So, I grabbed the knife,
and it just slid right out.
When he showed me his hand,
there was no blood, no hole.
Nothing to say
that there was just
a freaking knife
stabbed through his hand.
My 7-year-old brain
was just exploding...
So I asked him.
I asked him
how he did it.
What'd he say?
He said he could only share his
secrets with other magicians.
I went back last year and saw
that he was still there.
I showed him a few tricks,
we talked shop for a little bit.
And I told him the same exact
story I just told you.
Did he tell you
how he did the trick?
It wasn't a trick.
It was real.
I mean, for a year, this guy
stabbed a knife through his hand.
Each time, he cut a little deeper,
let the scar tissue grow.
Then do it again.
After a while, he had stabbed a
clean hole straight through.
And because of the scar tissue,
there was no blood.
So, when he performed,
he just covered
his hands with
a little bit of latex
and it'd look
like brand-new skin.
That's the effect.
I mean,
it's so obvious,
but you wouldn't think
anyone would go that far.
Yeah, he cut a freakin'
hole in his hand.
I mean, is all that
worth it just for a trick?
I mean, can't you do tricks
that don't hurt you?
Anyone can
learn a trick,
but doing something
no one else
is willing to do
makes you a magician.
I can do something
no one else can.
So, you think the spirit
is sitting in the right chair?
Yeah, I think so.
And you?
Yeah, I agree,
right chair.
I mean, are you sure?
You can change your mind,
'cause I'm going to ask it
to get up in a second.
Okay.
Spirit, would you
leave the table please?
Hey, man.
Yeah, I was heading
over there in a few.
Word. Later.
Yo!
This kid right here.
This kid's a little pimp.
Hey, do a shot with me.
To the young buck, Bo.
Go find yourself a boo.
Everybody, get naked.
Like, when I drop that mixtape,
dawg, it is fucking game over.
There are bars
on it, son.
Bars.
And I work with this cat
who's probably
gonna be producing
Ye's new album.
The good lord, Yeezus.
Bo, let me talk to you
for a sec.
Yo, Angelo,
where you been at?
Something came up.
Word.
I just wanted to ask you
something real quick.
Yeah, what's up?
Why the fuck are
you cutting my drugs?
I don't know what
you're talking about, man.
We're not gonna
play this game.
You ungrateful piece of shit!
I gave you a job when you needed it most,
and now you're fucking me?
How much did you cut it?
Just another kilo, man.
I swear I was
gonna pay you back.
Fucking hell.
I swear.
I swear. I swear.
No, no, no, no, no!
Come here,
you motherfucker.
Please, please.
No, no, no. No, no.
You know what?
I want my kilo's
full value back
without you taking a cut.
Obviously.
Another 15 since you
doubled my product.
And let's throw one more 15k on
top of that for asshole tax.
So, if you're
following me, that's 45k,
and I want it by
midnight next Sunday.
Get the fuck
out of my house.
Hey, close the door.
Bo, what happened?
I don't want Tina to see.
What happened? Hey.
I messed up, okay?
I messed up bad.
Tell me what happened.
If you never want to
see me again, I get it.
I mean, I really hate that I
was lying to you about it,
but, honestly, I thought
I'd be out of this by now.
You don't seem
like the type of girl
that'd want to
date a drug dealer.
Okay, stop.
I'm gonna help
you figure this out.
There's no way I can
get that kind of money.
I only have
$5,000 saved up.
Okay, but you have to try,
right?
If he's as bad as you say he is,
you don't have a choice.
Look, sell off what you have.
Keep performing until you can find a
way to get the rest of the money.
And I'll see
what I can do, too.
To working in hell.
$35,914.
You sold everything?
Everything.
Here.
What's this?
It's only $900.
Wait, where'd this
come from?
I had it saved up.
It was supposed to be
for school applications.
Holly...
You're not allowed
to give it back.
I don't even
know what to say...
You don't have
to say anything.
You know
I'll pay you back.
Yeah.
Now, how do I get nine grand
by midnight tomorrow?
Fuck!
Is something bad
going to happen to us?
What?
No.
You're scared.
I know.
I'm sorry, T.
It's just hard being a grown
up sometimes, that's all.
What's happening?
Nothing you need
to worry about.
Well, I hope
it's over soon.
I'm not gonna make it.
I've got six hours.
Then what are we
doing in an arcade, Bo?
Oh, my God!
Yes! I won! Oh, my God!
Hurry up.
Hey. Tina, Tina.
Let's get you
something to eat.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Here. Try this one.
What's the deal
with these things?
Maybe over here.
Come on...
Please, it's so close.
Come on, buddy,
you can do it.
And this time...
- Come on. Come on.
- Come on.
I did it.
Yes, yes! Oh, my God!
Yes! Yeah!
Yes! Okay,
let's go over here.
Over there.
...got a set on the 12th.
But we already have
somebody for the 14th.
Plus, you guys have always
done better on Saturdays.
I think it's
a bad idea, but...
How much?
Fifteen.
If that's what you wanna try.
You can take 'em off.
No, I mean, it's on you.
If you wanna take that risk.
I mean, look,
it doesn't matter to me.
Door set is the same,
no matter what.
Split on my end is fine,
so I mean...
It just depends on whether
you can bring people out.
All right,
you just let me know.
Hey. Sorry.
Okay, that is yours,
this is mine.
Are you taking off?
I might stick around.
Yeah, you should.
I'll buy you a drink.
I just got
some great news.
Okay.
You up to that?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Oh, man.
You been out here yet?
It's nuts. Nuts tonight.
Packed.
You gonna tell me
the good news, or no?
Yeah.
But it's good news,
so I'm telling you at the bar
with a drink in my hand.
Okay, well,
I'll meet you at the bar, then.
I'm just gonna hit
the bathroom real quick.
Oh, yeah.
No problem.
Fuck.
Shit.
Where the hell did you go?
I grabbed the wrong guest list.
There's a
party of eight under Speranza?
Yeah, they're good.
Coming back now.
All right,
what are you drinking?
Um, let me get
that one right there.
Which one?
That Casamigos there.
Oh, yeah.
That's good stuff.
So, I got a job.
Really?
Yeah, buddies of mine
have a band.
They're going on a tour next week.
It's shit money,
but it's not this.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Yeah. Thanks.
Yeah.
Hey, to getting out.
To getting out.
All right,
I'll catch you later.
Chase his ass,
and I'll go get the car.
Let's go, let's go.
What's up, boy?
Where you going, man?
Nah, nah, nah.
What's up, black star?
Where you going, man?
You piece of shit.
Got me out here
running around.
Let me see that.
What, you like games
or something?
Come on. Come on.
Shit.
Are you fucking serious?
Here.
Come here, come here.
- Hello?
- You got a watch?
Where's my money?
I'm almost there.
I just need a little more time.
I didn't ask for
you to get close, Bo.
I asked for 45k by
midnight tonight.
I just need
some more time.
I want another 5k.
Why couldn't I
go in the house?
Um...
I'm gonna pick you up
from school today, okay?
Okay.
All right.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Have a good day.
Okay.
I don't know
what else to do.
I can't get
any more money.
I did everything
that I could.
I don't know,
nothing's working.
Holly, I almost died.
What?
You and Tina have
got to get out of here.
You've gotta
get out of LA.
And I wanna
come with you.
But what about
school and your mom?
What you said
the other night,
that I don't deserve this.
I really needed
to hear that.
I do deserve better.
And you do, too.
Look, you guys could
get out of here now,
and I'd only be
a few weeks behind you.
My semester's
almost over,
and I could apply to some new
schools over the summer.
But where would we go?
Excuse me.
Have you seen my sister?
Tina? Tina Wolfe?
Yeah, I think your
uncle picked her up.
Uncle?
- T, where are you?
- Homie,
did you think I was kidding?
Angelo?
Get me my fucking money.
If you touch my...
Everything okay?
I know you're in class,
just wanted you to know that it's looking
like I'll be working late tonight.
I need you to snag T after school
and get her to dance class.
It's that studio on Walden.
She knows where.
I'll be out in plenty
of time to pick her up.
Oh, and there should
be a 20 on the fridge.
Go ahead and order
yourself something
if you get hungry
before we get back,
but no pizza tonight,
please?
Text me and let me know that
you got this message, okay?
All right? I love you.
End of message.
To replay this message,
press...
Bo?
Hey, Mr. Granger.
You all right?
I, uh...
Come in. Come in.
It's a little
complicated.
It always will be.
Anything I can do?
Do you remember the last
project I did senior year?
Bo.
Building an electromagnet
in a shoebox is one thing,
but in your arm?
How long has
this been infected?
I'm taking care of it.
It doesn't look like it.
The negative is
fed to my thumb
and the positive to
the rest of the fingers.
The board is programed to read
all the different inputs.
It gives me a little bit of
control over pitch, yaw and roll.
But I need more power.
I mean, the lithium-ions last a while,
but their output, it's just...
I need more output.
Have you always run the battery
straight to the electromagnet?
Yeah.
Huh.
What about
a feedback oscillator?
A feedback oscillator
would magnify the voltage.
You could do that
without touching the coil.
But with a higher voltage,
you'll be running into a new problem.
You see, these wires
in your arm are thin.
You'd want a larger gauge
with that much power,
otherwise,
it could overheat.
But it's still possible,
right?
Yeah.
I think so.
So, a feedback oscillator.
And a bigger battery.
Do you have
a soldering iron?
This isn't for a trick,
is it?
For what it's worth,
I didn't want to bail on the scholarship.
But I had to.
I just want you
to know that.
I do.
Thanks.
Please be careful.
Listen, uh, if I'm not back in a
half an hour, call the cops, okay?
It's like,
"You're so fat, why are you
"living in your
mother's house?"
Bo.
You gotta be out of
your fucking mind.
Everybody, get out! Get out!
Angelo!
What the hell is goin' on?
What the fuck
are you doing here?
You have my money?
Where's my sister?
Is she here?
That's not the deal.
Angelo, where the
hell is my sister?
Give me my money.
This had nothing
to do with Tina.
You crossed a line
when you took her.
Bo, the fucked-up thing about all this,
man, is that I liked you.
You did good work.
And you know what,
I invested in you.
But I'm getting so tired of people
who have no fucking respect.
I'm trying to build something here,
and every corner I turn,
there's another piece of shit who
thinks they can just fuck me over.
You did it behind my back,
you did it to my face.
I mean, where's the
common fucking decency?
I'm not gonna stand here and have
you roll up inside my house,
fucking my shit up,
telling me you deserve some shit.
So, let's make
this an example.
Not for you, but for the next
motherfucker who thinks it's a good idea
to fuck with Angelo.
What the hell?
Shit.
Where's Tina?
Shit! Fuck!
Where is she?
Oh, God!
Where's my sister?
Stop! Stop!
She's fine. She's fine.
Where is she?
Shit!
Stop! Oh, God!
She's with my aunt.
Where?
Okay, stop, stop.
3221 San Tempest.
All right, come on,
man, stop!
What the fuck, Bo?
Oh, gosh!
Please, leave, man.
I told you where she is.
She's fine.
Oh, come on! Look, we're good, all right?
We're good.
Just...
Just leave, all right?
Oh, shit!
$15,000.
One kilo.
What I actually owe you.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, shit.
Hey, are you okay?
Where's Tina?
We gotta go, she's close! Come on!
Okay, okay.
Thank you.
Hey. Wanna go?
Oh! Hey. Absolutely.
Thank you, guys.
T, go start your homework. Bo and I
are going to start dinner, okay?
Okay.
I had my test today.
Oh, yeah, I forgot to ask.
I got a B.
B's not bad.
Did you hear from Georgi?
Yeah, she should
be here this weekend.
Sweet.
What'd you do today?
Just working
on that new trick.
Are you ever
gonna show me?
When it's ready.
It's gonna be something special.
Bo.
Oh, my God!